1. createstorage.py creates a database for all decks,
then import.py lets you import a deck
for example from archidekt.com with
the format: "1x Odric, Lunarch Marshall"
2. createruntime.py creates the database for the game session.
After that start the backendchoosedeck.py and access the
frontendchoosedeck.html to choose a deck and enter a name
for the game.
3. Wait for me to finish the API with all the calls and somehow 
get the frontend, and we're good